holidayphone.com 2018-08-30

# Security & Privacy

SNSGap-International BV respects the privacy of all users of its site and ensures that the personal information you provide is treated confidentially. We will use your information only with your permission . SNSGap-International BV will not sell your personal data to third parties and will only be made available to third parties that are involved in processing your order and if you have given us permission to do so.

If you create an account with SNSGap-International BV we save your data . In this account we store information such as your name and address , telephone number, email address and payment information, so you do not need to enter this with each new order

**Your personal information is safe with SNSGap-International BV.  
**

We appreciate the trust you place in us and we will therefore be extremely careful with your data. We use SSL (Secure Socket Layer ) to send your data. Encrypted SSL is one of the most safe techniques . Your data will always be protected and kept confidential.

.  

**Cookies  **

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer by your browser. SNSGap-International BV may use cookies to recognize you when you visit you. Cookies enable us to collect information about the use of our services and to improve and adapt to the needs of our visitors . Information Our cookies provide information related to personal identification . You can set your browser to notify you when you shop with us that no cookies are needed

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy of SNSGap-International BV , questions please send an email to [info@snsgap-international.com](mailto:info@ams-distribution.com) . Our customer service will help you if you need information about your data or if you want to change anything. You have the right to correct your data . In case our Privacy Policy are needed, you will find on this page the most recent information.
